export const mmaQuestions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    questionText: "Which fighter has competed in WWE and UFC?",
    options: {
      optionOne: 'John Cena',
      optionTwo: 'Jon Jones',
      optionThree: 'Brock Lesnar',
      optionFour: 'Alex Pereira'
    },
    answer: 'Brock Lesnar'
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    questionText: 'Which fighter is known as the "Beast Incarnate"?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Brock Lesnar',
      optionTwo: 'Francis Ngannou',
      optionThree: 'Cyril Gane',
      optionFour: 'Quinton Jackson'
    },
    answer: 'Brock Lesnar'
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    questionText: 'Israel Adesanya suffered his first UFC defeat to?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Anderson Silva',
      optionTwo: 'Dricus Du Plesis',
      optionThree: 'Sean Strickland',
      optionFour: 'Alex Pereira'
    },
    answer: 'Alex Pereira'
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    questionText: 'How many rounds are in a UFC non-title fight?',
    options: {
      optionOne: '5',
      optionTwo: '4',
      optionThree: '3',
      optionFour: '6'
    },
    answer: '3'
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    questionText: 'How many minutes does a UFC round last?',
    options: {
      optionOne: '5',
      optionTwo: '4',
      optionThree: '3',
      optionFour: '6'
    },
    answer: '5'
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    questionText: 'Which weight class does UFC fighter Jon Jones currently fight in?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'light Heavy Weight',
      optionTwo: 'Heavy Weight',
      optionThree: 'Middle Weight',
      optionFour: 'Bantam weight'
    },
    answer: 'Heavy Weight'
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    questionText: 'Who is the current UFC Middle Weight Champion?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Dricus Du Plesis',
      optionTwo: 'Alex Pereira',
      optionThree: 'Israel Adesanya',
      optionFour: 'Sean Strickland'
    },
    answer: 'Dricus Du Plesis'
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    questionText: 'Who is the only UFC fighter that has lost to no one than himself?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Anderson Silva',
      optionTwo: 'Jon Jones',
      optionThree: 'Daniel DC Cormier',
      optionFour: 'Tom Aspinall'
    },
    answer: 'Jon Jones'
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    questionText: "Who became the youngest champion in UFC history with his title victory over Maur√≠cio Rua at age 23?",
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Rashad Evans',
      optionTwo: 'Quinton Jackson',
      optionThree: 'Jon Jones',
      optionFour: 'Israel Adesanya'
    },
    answer: 'Jon Jones'
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    questionText: "Which UFC fighter lost his title defence giving Jon Jones his first Heavy weight Title'?",
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Daniel Cormier',
      optionTwo: 'Cyril Gane',
      optionThree: 'Alexander Gustafson',
      optionFour: 'Stipe Miocic'
    },
    answer: 'Cyril Gane'
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    questionText: 'Which UFC fighter is nicknamed "The Mighty Mouse"?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Francis Ngannou',
      optionTwo: 'Demetrious Johnson',
      optionThree: 'Brock Lesnar',
      optionFour: 'Max Holloway'
    },
    answer: 'Demetrious Johnson'
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    questionText: 'Anderson Silva competed in which division?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Heavy Weight',
      optionTwo: 'Middle Weight',
      optionThree: 'Fly Weight',
      optionFour: 'Bantam Weight'
    },
    answer: 'Middle Weight'
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    questionText: 'Which Fighter is nicknamed "Poatan a.k.a Hands of Stone"?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Chuck Lidell',
      optionTwo: 'Ilia Topuria',
      optionThree: 'Alex Periera',
      optionFour: 'Francis Ngannou'
    },
    answer: 'Alex Periera'
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    questionText: 'With 29 wins and no losses on his card, Which fighter held the record of being the longest reigning light weight champion in UFC history?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Khabib Nurmagedov',
      optionTwo: 'Justin Poirier',
      optionThree: 'Conor McGregor',
      optionFour: 'Nate Diaz'
    },
    answer: 'Khabib Nurmagedov'
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    questionText: ' In which weight class does the Aussie dynamo Robert Whittaker unleash his fury in the UFC?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Heavy Weight',
      optionTwo: 'Fly Weight',
      optionThree: 'Light Weight',
      optionFour: 'Middle Weight'
    },
    answer: 'Middle Weight'
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    questionText: 'Which gritty MMA fighter became a YouTube sensation, famed for his raw street brawls and larger-than-life persona?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Chuck Lidell',
      optionTwo: 'Kimbo Slice',
      optionThree: 'Robin Whittaker',
      optionFour: 'Rashad Evans'
    },
    answer: 'Kimbo Slice'
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    questionText: 'Which UFC fighter was the first to hold UFC Championships in 2 weight classes simultaneously (Feather and Light weight Championship)?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Micheal Bisping',
      optionTwo: 'Khabib Nurmagedov',
      optionThree: 'Conor McGregor',
      optionFour: 'Demetrious Johnson'
    },
    answer: 'Conor McGregor'
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    questionText: 'Who is the President of the UFC?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Donald Trump',
      optionTwo: 'Dana White',
      optionThree: 'Jose Aldo',
      optionFour: 'Eddie Hearn'
    },
    answer: 'Dana White'
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    questionText: 'Which UFC fighter had a 16-fight winning streak from June 2006 to July 2013?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Anderson Silva',
      optionTwo: 'George St-Pierre',
      optionThree: 'Chuck Lidell',
      optionFour: 'Jon Jones'
    },
    answer: 'Anderson Silva'
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    questionText: 'What year was the UFC founded??',
    answerOptions: [
      { answerText: '1983', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: '1993', isCorrect: true },
      { answerText: '2003', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: '2009', isCorrect: false },
    ],
    options: {
      optionOne: '1983',
      optionTwo: '1993',
      optionThree: '2003',
      optionFour: '2009'
    },
    answer: '1993'
  }
]